嘿 我看到有人发明了一种办法
Hey, I read that someone invented a way
可以将走路的能量转化成电磁能
to convert your footsteps into electromagnetic energy
这样就一边走一边能给手机充电了
so you can charge your cell phone while walking.
我们几年前就想到了这主意
We had that idea years ago.
怎么就没有进一步研究呢?
How come we never did anything with it?
也许是因为我们把图落在了餐厅
Probably because we left the diagram of it in the restaurant,
没一个愿意走回去取
and none of us wanted to walk back.
我知道你不进一步研究的真正原因
I know the real reason you never made progress with that idea.
你是在2007年
You thought of it
9月22日想到的
September 22, 2007.
两天后 Penny搬了进来
Two days later, Penny moved in,
你的血液都跑去生殖器了
and so much blood rushed to your genitals,
所以大脑就空了
your brain became a ghost town.
不是这么回事
That's not what happened.
我记得很清楚
I remember it distinctly
是因为我刚写完每年一次
because I had just composed my annual poem
纪念苏斯博士逝世周年的诗歌
commemorating the anniversary of Dr. Seuss's death.
苏斯博士: 著名儿童作品作家
没人想听
No one wants to hear it.
为什么会死?
Why, die.
为什么他会死?
Why did he die?
老了 说了
Old, told.
我听说他老了
I was told he was old.
Penny不是我没有深入研究的原因
Penny is not the reason I didn't pursue that idea.
真的? 那认识她以后
Oh, really? Since meeting her,
你最大的成就是什么?
what have been your greatest accomplishments?
简单
Easy.
和Penny上床
Sleeping with Penny.
在Penny甩了他之后 把她争取了回来
Getting Penny to go back out with him after she dumped him.
骗Penny订婚
Tricking Penny into getting engaged.
几个星期前 他差点做成一个引体向上
And a few weeks ago, he almost did a pull-up.
我觉得有人该道歉
I think someone owes me an apology.
别自责
Well, don't feel bad.
我觉得在姑娘们进入我们生活后
I think we've all been distracted
我们都被分神了
since the girls entered our lives.
你承认Amy让你分神了?
You admit Amy's a distraction?
太分神了 听听这个
Oh, very much so. Listen to this.
两天前收到的
This is from two days ago.
"嗨 希望你今天愉快"
"Hi. Hope you're having a good day."
有谁会一直这样短信调情?
Who has time for this constant sexting?
也许我们分散了注意力
Well, maybe we have lost our focus.
再聚到一起进行头脑风暴也不是件坏事
It wouldn't kill us to get together and brainstorm ideas.
哦 我们可以来一次静思
Ooh, we could have one of those retreats.
我们独特的科学静思
Like our own science retreat.
我表哥在森林里有个小木屋
My cousin has a cabin out in the woods.
我可不去森林里的小木屋
I'm not going to a cabin in the woods.
你没看过"林中小屋"吗?
Did you see the movie Cabin in the Woods?
林中小屋: 惊悚恐怖电影
那我们就去酒店
Then we'll go to a hotel.
酒店? 没看过"闪灵"吗?
A hotel? Did you see The Shining?
闪灵: 惊悚恐怖电影
我们可以北上
We could go up
去大熊湖的湖畔小屋
to Big Bear and get a house on the lake.
你没看过"湖边小屋"?
Did you see The Lake House?
湖边小屋: 爱情悬疑电影
"湖边小屋"里又没发生什么坏事
Nothing bad happens in The Lake House.
对他们是没坏事 对我有
Yeah, well, no, not to them. To me.
什么穿越时空的信箱
Time traveling mailbox.
对我来说穿越的
The only time that traveled
就只是我浪费的那一个半小时
was an hour and half of my life down the toilet.
好吧 那我们就留在这里好了
Fine. Then we'll just stay here and do it.
你还没提议海边小屋呢
Well, you didn't suggest a beach house.
你想去海边小屋?
You would go to a beach house?
天啊 当然不想... 没看过"大白鲨"吗?
Well, good Lord, no... have you seen Jaws?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第5集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子   时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 影子酱 轮子君   校对: UU爆炸了
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
我和兄弟们讨论
So, the guys and I are talking
想要在这个周末做个科学静思
about having kind of a science retreat this weekend.
只是想问问你可以吗
I just wanted to know if that's okay.
我们本来说好星期天一起吃早午餐的...
You and I had talked about going to brunch on Sunday...
周末想去拉斯维加斯吗?
Want to go to Vegas this weekend?
当然想去
Of course I do.
Bernadette呢?
Bernadette?
女生周末去维加斯 一起吗?
Girl's weekend. Vegas. You in?
当然啦! 一起去!
Hell, yeah! Yes!
- 我来查机票  - 我来查酒店
- I'll check flights.  - I'll check hotels.
我来查内裤 我可能兴奋到尿裤子了
I'll check my underpants. I'm so excited, I think I peed.
她们好像不反对
They seem okay with it.
嘿
Hey.
- 嘿  - 嘿 我还以为你来不了呢
- Hey.  - Hey. I didn't think you'd make it.
- 为什么?  - 因为你现在
- Why not?  - Well, 'cause you have
有了固定女朋友 所以我们觉得
a steady girlfriend now, and we assumed
你得待在家里 陪她做点饭后运动
you'd have to stay home to lower the food down to her in the pit.
那我得告诉你 Emily今晚要干活
For your information, Emily is working tonight.
是啊 要结束"运动"也是蛮拼的呢
Yeah, one would assume, on getting out of the pit.
好了 集中注意力
Okay, let's focus.
姑娘们走了 我们有48个小时
The girls are gone, we have 48 hours.
没人能让我们分神 一起改变世界吧
There are no distractions. Let's change the world.
思考状态启动 我们开始
Thinking caps on. Here we go.
哦 太兴奋了 我们在创新
Ooh, this is exciting. We're innovating.
感觉就像在演"脸书"电影
I feel like we're in the Facebook movie.
我没看过
Oh. I never saw that.
- 不是吧?  - 哦
- Yeah. Really?  - Oh.
很好看的 而且我发誓不是因为贾斯汀·汀布莱克
It's wonderful, and I swear I'm not saying that
参演了才这么说的
because Justin Timberlake is in it.
我有蓝光盘
Yeah, I have it on Blu-ray.
我们应该看看
We should watch it.
好 我做点爆米花
Cool. I'll make the popcorn.
各位...
Guys...
过了30秒 我们就从
in 30 seconds, we went from
"一起改变世界吧"变成"一起看电影吧"了
"Let's change the world" to "Let's watch TV."
抱歉 你是不同意吗?
I'm sorry. Is that a "no"?
好吧 不
Okay. No.
Leonard说得对 我们得集中精力
Leonard's right. We're here to focus.
我们以前不是有点子清单吗?
Didn't we used to have a list of all our ideas?
我想... 我还留着
I... I think I still have it.
我还没听到明确答复
I did not get a clear answer.
就暂时先放一边了
I'm gonna set this down now.
找到了
Ah, here it is.
哇哦
Whoa.
我好多年都没看过了
I haven't looked at these in years.
"机器人女友"
"Robot girlfriend."
是我的主意
Mm, that was mine.
"机器人妓女"
"Robot prostitute."
还是我的
Also mine.
等等 我有点奇怪
Wait. I'm confused.
你为什么会想要机器人女友
Why would you need both a robot girlfriend
又要机器人妓女呢?
and a robot prostitute?
因为有些事情你没法
There's just some things you don't do
跟机器人女友做
with your robot girlfriend.
兄弟 你遇到Bernadette之后
Boy, when you met Bernadette,
机器人研究领域受到了重创啊
the field of robotics really took a hit.
好吧 我们就跳过
Okay, let's just skip
那些能"搞"的发明
all the inventions you can have sex with.
好吧... 有了:
All right, no... here we go:
"符合人体工程学的加热坐垫"
"Ergonomic heated seat cushion""
那个会震动 下一个
No, it vibrates. Keep going.
好吧 我们还是想些新点子吧
You know, let's just come up with something new.
要知道
You know,
相当一部分的伟大创新都是从科幻作品里
a number of significant innovations have been inspired
找到的灵感
by science fiction.
地球同步人造卫星是借鉴了Arthur C. Clarke的作品
The... the geosynchronous satellite from Arthur C. Clarke.
Arthur C. Clarke: 英国科幻作家
摩托罗拉翻盖手机... 借鉴了"星际迷航"
The Motorola flip phone... that came from Star Trek.
我已经怀疑了很久
Yeah, and I've long suspected that the idea
一个非洲裔美国人当总统这主意
of an African-American President was stolen
是从"天地大冲撞"里偷来的
from the movie Deep Impact.
嘿
Hey,
他们在"回到未来II"里演的未来
the future they show in Back to the Future II
就是明年
is only a year away.
那电影里面有好多东西还没发明出来呢
A lot of the things in that movie haven't been invented yet.
如果我们能把其中一个
How cool would that be
在现实中制造出来有多棒呀?
if we could make one of those a reality?
如果我们能弄明白Marty悬浮滑板的
If we could figure out the scientific basis
科学理论依据
for Marty's hover board,
就能在全世界投入应用了
that would have universal application.
这东西... 只适用于绝对零度
Well, it's... it's possible at absolute zero,
但我们得想办法解决
but we would have to remove
温度的限制
the temperature restrictions.
我有个主意
Oh, I have an idea.
我觉得我也想到了
I think I have the same one.
我们得看一遍"回到未来II"!
We got to watch Back to the Future II!
我去做爆米花
I'll make the popcorn.
我们先去哪里?
So, where should we go first?
哦
Ooh.
酒吧有翻唱乐队表演
There's a cover band in the lounge.
- 不去  - 但他们唱的是巴瑞·曼尼洛的歌
- Nah.  - But they play Barry Manilow.
- 不去  - 但他们叫"酷似曼尼洛"
- No.  - But they're called "Fairly Manilow""
好吧
Oh. Okay.
- 太好了!  - 不去!
- Great!  - No!
那你想干什么?
Well, what do you want to do?
我们在维加斯
Well, we're in Vegas.
我想去楼下 来一大杯玛格丽特鸡尾酒
I want to go downstairs, get a bucket of margaritas,
跳舞跳到吐在轮盘赌桌上
dance until I vomit all over a roulette wheel
然后看它飞溅四方
and watch it go everywhere.
如果我们不想吐呢?
What if we don't want to vomit?
你会吐的 所以他们才卖一大杯
Oh, you will. That's why they give you the bucket.
- 糟糕  - 怎么了?
- Uh-oh.  - What?
我老板来短信
It's my boss.
他们把我的现场实习提前到了周一
They moved my field ride up to Monday.
那是什么意思?
What does that mean?
就意味着我没有一个星期可以看材料了
It means instead of having a week to study,
只有两天
I only have two days.
太糟糕了
That sucks.
你能早上再看吗?
Can you start in the morning?
有很多东西要看
Uh, it's kind of a lot.
好吧 我今晚看一些
You know, let me do a little tonight,
晚点再和你们一起玩
and I'll catch up with you guys later.
- 你确定吗?  - 没关系的 你们去吧
- You sure?  - Yeah, it's okay. Go ahead.
现在Penny不去了...
So, um, now that Penny's not coming...
- 我们不去看"酷似曼尼洛"  - 好吧
- We're not seeing Fairly Manilow.  - Okay.
等等 暂停
Hold on. Pause.
有地方不对劲 听着...
Something doesn't make sense. Look...
2015年 Biff偷了运动年鉴
In 2015, Biff steals the sports almanac
然后拿了时光机器
and takes the time machine
回到1955年 就为了把年鉴给年轻的自己
back to 1955, to give it to his younger self.
但一旦他这么做了 他就改变了未来
But as soon as he does that, he changes the future,
所以他回到的那个2015年
so the 2015 he returns to would be
就是个不一样的2015年 而不是Marty和博士在的2015年了
a different 2015, not the 2015 that Marty and Doc were in.
这和"热浴盆时光机"完全一样
This is Hot Tub Time Machine all over again.
如果未来的Biff
If future Biff goes back to 2015
一把年鉴交给年轻Biff就回2015年的话
right after he gives young Biff the almanac,
他就能回到有Marty和博士的那个2015年
he could get back to the 2015 with Marty and Doc in it.
因为1955年的Biff是到了
Because it wasn't until his 21st birthday
21岁生日的时候才赌了第一次
that 1955 Biff placed his first bet.
等等 等等
Wait. Whoa, whoa.
用"赌了"不对吧?
Is "placed" right?
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
用"赌了"来形容
Is "placed" the right tense
本该在被未来某物影响的过去的未来
for something that would have happened in the future
发生的事情 时态对吗?
of a past that was affected by something from the future?
在未来的过去的未来赌了?
Had will have placed?
干得漂亮
That's my boy.
好吧 1955年的Biff是到了
Okay, so, it wasn't until his 21st birthday
21岁生日的时候才在未来的过去的未来赌了第一次
that Biff had will have placed his first bet
赚了百万
and made his millions.
那时候他才改变了时间线
That's when he altered the timeline.
没错 但他没有在过去的未来的过去赌!
Yeah, but he had will haven't placed it!
什么?!
What?!
和"热浴盆时光机"不同
Unlike Hot Tub Time Machine,
这个简直太简单了
this couldn't be more simple.
当Biff在1955年拿到了年鉴
When Biff gets the almanac in 1955,
他创造的未来就不是
the alternate future he creates isn't the one
Marty和Brown博士会用时光机器
in which Marty and Doc Brown ever use the time machine
去的2015年
to travel to 2015.
因此
Therefore,
在新的时间线里
in the new timeline,
Marty和Doc从来没有带过来那个时间机器...
Marty and Doc never brought the time machine...
等... 等等
W-Wait.
“带来”?
Is "brought" right?
Marty和Doc从来没有过已经带来过?
Marty and Doc never had have had brought?
我不知道 你让我这么纠结
I don't know. You did it to me.
哦 那就这么用了
Oh, I'm going with it.
Marty和Doc从来没有过已经把
Marty and Doc never had have had brought
时间机器带到2015年
the time machine to 2015.
那就意味着2015年的BIff也
That means 2015 Biff could also
没有过已经带给1955年的Biff过年鉴
not had have had brought the almanac to 1955 Biff.
所以 在1955年Biff得到年鉴的时间线
Therefore, the timeline in which 1955 Biff gets the almanac
也同样是
is also the timeline
没有得到年鉴的1955年的Biff所在的时间线
in which 1955 Biff never gets the almanac.
并且还不仅仅是“没有得到”
And not just "never gets."
从来没有过 没有不是过 从来没有没有过
Never have, never hasn't, never had have hasn't.
他说得对
He's right.
而且 Biff是哪门子名字?
Also, what kind of name is Biff?
听起来像开饼干罐头的声音
Sounds like when you pop open a can of Pillsbury dough.
哔夫
Biff.
喔 那东西配小香肠简直是人间美味
Oh, that stuff is so good wrapped around cocktail weenies.
又来了...
Guys...
你们知道“鸡鸡”这个词
Do you know that the word "wiener"
来自于德语中的
comes from the German name
奥地利首都维也纳 “维也鸡鸡”?
of the Austrian capital Vienna, or "Wien"?
你知不知道奥地利的地图
Do you know if you look at Austria on a map
看起来就像是一个鸡鸡?
it actually looks like a wiener?
我们在干嘛啊
Guys, what are we doing?
我... 我们把妹子们都打发走了
W-We sent the girls away
这样我们就能专注一点
so we could focus.
好像没用
I don't think it worked.
说不定喝完这之后 你会有心情听听曼尼洛的歌
Maybe after this, you'll be in the mood for some Manilow.
我觉得喝完这个我就挂了
I think after this, I'll be dead.
看看我俩在外面浪
Look at us out,
Penny却在房间里学习
while Penny's in the room studying.
我很为她骄傲
I'm proud of her.
这是个不错的机会
This is a great opportunity.
看到她那么认真对待这件事 我很高兴
It's nice to see her take it seriously.
的确
It is.
不说Penny了
But enough about Penny.
我们聊聊自己吧
Let's talk about us.
我们看起来很不错
We're looking good.
是啊
We are...
不能更棒了
Better than good.
看看你 火辣的不行了
I mean, look at you. Your body's bangin'!
Amy啊!
Amy!
别这样Amy Amy地叫
Don't "Amy" me.
我们总是讨论Penny有多性感
We're always talking about how hot Penny is.
来 来场科学家之间的对话
Come on... scientist to scientist,
强子对撞机(胸)有多大?
how big are those Hadron Colliders?
你让我好尴尬
You're embarrassing me.
噢 别害羞嘛
Oh, don't be embarrassed.
给你看看我脊椎里的草皮
I'll show you the divot in my spine.
- 什么?  - 不不不 没关系的 那是天生的
- What?  - No, no, it's okay. I was born with it.
如果你在这儿放一个AA电池
If you put a double-A battery in there,
我的腿会自动踢人
it makes my leg kick.
好吧
All right.
哦 这里就好多了
Oh, this is already better. There are
这儿的干扰要少得多
far fewer distractions in here.
而且 这里是我们的思维
Plus, this is where our minds
习惯于专心工作的地方
are conditioned to focus on work.
我在考虑着配电板的问题
So, I've been thinking about the hover boards,
也许我们可以利用磁悬浮技术
and maybe there's a way we could use maglev technology.
或者我们可以想出来过度冷却那些材料的方法
Or if we could figure out a way to supercool the materials,
我们可以利用量子耦合
we could utilize quantum coupling.
不知道有没有人试过
Well, I wonder if anyone's tried that.
上网查查看
Go online and look it up.
喔 我不能反驳他
Oh, I can't argue with him.
屏幕上清楚的显示着
It's right there on the screen.
奥地利确实看起来像鸡鸡
Austria does look like a wiener.
那还不是最高能的
That's nothing, dude.
去查查佛罗里达州看起来有多"雄起"
Go check out how hung Florida is.
我确信佛罗里达先生走起路来一定搞笑
I'm sure Mrs. Florida's walking funny.
我们可以回到工作上了吗?
Can we get back to work?
嗯... 他说得对
Yeah... he's right.
噢 我有个想法
Oh, here's a thought.
不如我们用操控制约的方法
What if we use some form of operant conditioning techniques
来避免我们偏离话题吧?
to keep us from getting off topic?
比如行为矫正法?
Like behavior modification?
对对对 就是那样
Yeah, exactly.
你知道
Did you know
那些技术实际上是被用来训练鸽子
those techniques were used to actually teach pigeons
打乒乓球的吗?
to play ping-pong?
不可能吧
That cannot be true.
嘿 都到赛点了!
Hey, it was match point.
一些心理学家
Some psychologists
通过惩罚来制约实验对象
perform operant conditioning with punishment.
没准我们能想出个方式
Maybe we can come up with a punishment
来惩罚那些偏移话题的人
for straying off topic.
不让人看谁赢了鸽子乒乓赛就是一种惩罚
Not getting to see who wins at pigeon ping-pong comes to mind.
每当我们分心的时候
We could snap a rubber band on our wrists
我们可以在手腕上贴个条
every time we get sidetracked.
唔 不错 在中世纪
Mmm, not bad. You know, in medieval times,
那些乱走题的是被惩罚带一个叫
idle chatter was punished with a device called
叫毒蛇钩的东西
the scold's bridle.
那是一个
It's an iron cage
刺穿舌头然后锁住整个头的铁笼子
that's locked around the head and pierces the tongue.
要是我们有一个就好了
If only we had one.
喔 我来看看亚马逊有没有
Oh! I'll check Amazon.
客房服务!
Housekeeping!
我们收到了一个
We had a complaint
关于有人在派对上大便的投诉!
about somebody pooping on a party in there!
其实是我俩啦!
It was us the whole time!
为什么告诉她? 刚刚都骗到她了
Why'd you tell her? It was working.
真的吗?
Was it working?
是啊
Yeah.
哦 不好意思
Oh, I'm so sorry.
看起来你们玩得很爽啊
You guys look like you're having fun.
我们爽得飞起来了
We're having the best time.
猜猜谁掷骰子赢了100块
Guess who won $100 playing craps.
那是个一块钱
That's a dollar.
那么猜猜谁对酒吧招待慷慨解囊了
Then guess who wildly overtipped a cocktail waitress.
嘿，Penny... 嘿 走吧
Hey, Penny... hey, let's go.
我们找到了一个有澳大利亚脱衣舞郎的地方
We found a place that has Australian male strippers.
我们想看看
We want to see
他们是不是扭屁股也是反向的
if they twirl their junk in the other direction.
听上去很棒
That sounds so great.
但我还有些东西要学
But I have a little more studying to do.
学霸的世界我们不懂
Can you believe this nerd?
来吧 你想屌丝地坐在这儿
Come on, do you want to sit here being a loser,
还是想看我
or do you want to watch me climb
如同一个袋鼠宝宝一般
into an Australian man's G-string
钻进一个澳洲男人的丁字裤里?
like a baby kangaroo?
好吧好吧 姐妹们 我真的很想跟你们出去
All right, guys, look, I would love to go out,
但我必须把这些东西弄完 明白么?
but I've got to get this done, okay?
所以祝你们在酒吧里玩的开心
So have fun at the club. And if you get
如果遇上麻烦了 找警察
in trouble, find a policeman.
不过如果他开始脱裤子了
And if he's taking off his pants,
他不是一个真正的警察
he is not a real policeman.
好吧 好吧 这东西显然对她很重要
Okay, okay, this is obviously very important to her.
让我们帮她一把这样她就能早点解放了
Let's just, we'll help her study so she can get done quicker.
来来来 我来考考你
Here... here, I'm gonna quiz you.
我来考考你
I'm gonna quiz you.
你的笔记在我手上了!
I got your notes!
在我手上!
我手上! 想拿到它们
I got your notes! If you want these,
就到脱衣舞酒吧来吧!
they're gonna be at the strip club!
你不去追她吗?
Aren't you gonna chase her?
追到衣帽间里?当然
To the walk-in closet? Sure.
那么我们达成共识
Okay, so we agree,
只要有人转移话题
whenever someone takes us off topic
他的手臂就得被拔个精光
they get their arm hair yanked off.
我可不能让那事发生
And I really can't let that happen
不然帮我做眼睫毛的女孩
or the girl who does my eyebrows will think
就会觉得我对她不忠
I've been cheating on her.
那么现在开始 量子耦合的好处是...
All right, now, one benefit of quantum coupling...
等等 不 我有问题:
Wait, no, question:
谁来决定某人是否脱离话题了
who decides if someone's gone off topic?
那应该会很明显吧 不然我们就投票决定
I think it'll be pretty clear. If not, we'll take a vote.
噢 而且...
Oh, and also...
嗷!
Ow!
我... 我们还没投票呢!
W-We didn't vote!
我们没必要投... 刚刚显然离题了
We didn't have to... that was clearly a tangent.
快点 回到正事上
Now come on. Back to work.
如果我们倾向于量子耦合...
If we're leaning towards quantum coupling...
啊! 干嘛?
Aah! Why?
你说了“量子耦合”
You said "quantum coupling."
那让我想到了"时空怪客"
That made me think of the show Quantum Leap.
(NBC于1989年与1993年间播映的科幻电视影集)
是你偏离了正题
That's a tangent and it's your fault.
太荒谬了 Sheldon 我投票那没有离题
That's ridiculous. Sheldon, I vote that is not a tangent.
谢谢 现在我欠你一次
Thank you. And now I owe you one.
嗷!
Ow!
都是你害的
That was your fault.
嘿!
Hey!
喔，粘掉了不少毛
Ooh, that is a lot of hair.
嗷!
Ow!
于是我得听Jenny抱怨了
And now I'm gonna hear it from Jenny.
都停下来
Everyone stop.
这真是个蠢主意
This was a stupid idea.
负面奖励毫无作用
Negative reinforcement isn't working.
我觉得你想说的是正效惩罚
I think you mean positive punishment.
负面奖励是指把利好刺激给移除
Negative reinforcement is the removal of a positive stimulus.
这是个常见错误
It's a common mistake.
负面奖励这种说法真的是不对的吗?
Negative reinforcement is really wrong?
哦 它一直被错误地使用
Oh, it's used incorrectly all the time.
连比尔·默里在拍摄"捉鬼敢死队"
Even Bill Murray makes that mistake
(比尔·默里 美国著名演员 "周六夜现场秀"节目创办人)
第一个镜头时都犯了这个错
in the first scene of Ghostbusters.
不可能 比尔·默里不可能错
No way. Not Bill Murray.
我在研究负面奖励在
I'm studying the effect of negative reinforcement
超能感官上的作用
on ESP ability.
啧啧
Huh.
比尔·默里确实搞错了
Bill Murray did get it wrong.
快进到棉花糖人那段
Jump ahead to the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man.
不要嘛!
No!
Leonard说的对
Leonard's right.
我们不能快进
We can't just jump ahead.
我们应该把全片看一遍
We have to watch the whole movie. Look.
我们一直在拖延
We keep procrastinating.
我们看了"回到未来II"
We saw Back to the Future II,
鸽子们玩乒乓球
pigeons playing ping-pong,
一堆形状像生殖器的国家
a bunch of countries that look like genitals
和一个生殖器像丹麦地图一样的人
and one guy whose genitals look like Denmark!
呃 不好意思点了那个视频
Yeah, sorry for clicking on that.
不早了 我们浪费了好多时间
It's late. We've wasted hours.
我们今晚就不能
Can we please find it in ourselves
稍微做点什么吗?
to do any amount of work tonight?
但是我们还没看到他们捉到任何一个鬼
But we didn't see them bust one ghost.
所以你是说大周六晚上的我们应该站在
So y... you're saying we should stand here
我的实验室里
in my lab on a Saturday night
用一台破笔记本把剩下的"活捉敢死队"
and watch the rest of Ghostbusters
给看完?
on a crappy laptop?
不是啊
No.
# 如果你家附近有些奇怪的事情 #
# If there's something strange in your neighborhood #
# －你应该找谁? －捉鬼敢死队! #
# - Who you gonna call?  - Ghostbusters! #
这倒真还不错嘛
It really does hold up.
看? 是不是比宾馆好玩多了?
See? Isn't this better than a hotel room?
是啊 摇摆起来!
Yep. Shake that thing!
你见过这么健美的身体么?
Have you ever seen a body so fine?
我在解剖课上见过一些挺有型的尸体
We had some pretty hot corpses in my anatomy class,
但没有哪个像这样能动的!
but none of them moved like that!
早上好!
Good morning.
你们想去游泳池玩吗?
You want to go to the pool?
来嘛... 你自己说过的
Come on... you said it yourself.
只有书呆子和屌丝才宅在房间里
Only nerds and losers stay in the room.
噢! 噢! 噢!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
哇 外面好晴朗
Wow, it's bright out.
不是吗? 我是不是该把窗帘拉上
Isn't it bright? I should probably close these curtains.
想多了 拜拜!
Nah. Bye!
你能把窗帘拉上吗?
Would you please close the drapes?
好吧
Okay.